afterdownload.com 2016-12-21

# ironSource Display Privacy Policy

                                       ironSource Display Privacy Policy
                                          Last Revised: February 1, 2016
ironSource Ltd. and its affiliate (“ironSource", "Company" “we” or "us") respect the privacy of the users
(“User” or “you”) of its website at the address http://display.ironsrc.com/ (the "Site") including our
proprietary ad serving service (“Service”) and is committed to protect the personal information that its
Users share with it. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we
may collect and use when you use our Site. It is hereby made clear that the term "Site" shall include the
"Service" provided therein.
1.       Your Consent (PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!)
BY ACCESSING THE SITE AND/OR USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND
CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THE "PRIVACY POLICY"), INCLUDING
TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED
BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE
SITE.
2.       Which information we may collect on our Users?
We may collect two types of data and information from our Users:
The first type of information is non-identifiable and anonymous information (“Non-personal
Information”). We are not aware of the identity of the User from which we have collected the Non-
personal Information. Non-Personal Information is any unconcealed information which is available to us
while Users are using the Site. Non-personal Information which is being gathered consists of technical
information and behavioral information, and may contain, among other things, the activity of the User on
the Site, type of operation system, User's 'click-stream' on the Site, browser and keyboard language, device
manufacturer, device model etc.
The second type of information is individually identifiable information (“Personal Information”). This
information may identify an individual or may be of a private and/or sensitive nature.
             a. Users of the Site automatically provide their IP address and as applicable, GAID/IDFA.
             b. In addition, Personal Information which is being gathered consists of any personal details
                  provided consciously and voluntarily by the User. The Personal Information is collected
                  from the details the Users provide in the sign-up on on the Site which requires e-mail
                  address, name, password, publisher name, country and web site URL. The User can
                  optionally fill in his/her daily impressions, and top trafficked country.
For avoidance of doubt, any Non-Personal Information connected or linked to any Personal Information
shall be deemed as Personal Information as long as such connection or linkage exists.
We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your approval, which
is obtained, inter alia, through your acceptance to the this Privacy Policy.
3.       How Do We Collect Information on Our Users?
There are two main methods we use:
             a. We collect information through your use of the Site. In other words, when you are using
                  the Site we are aware of it and may gather, collect and record the information relating to
                  such usage, either independently or through the help of third-party services as detailed
                  below.
             b. We collect information which you provide us voluntarily. For example, we collect
                  Personal information which you voluntarily provide when you fill in the sign-up in order

                 to sign you up for the Services. We store the Personal Information either independently or
                 through the help of our authorized third-party service providers as detailed below.
4.      What are the Purposes of the Collection of Information?
    Non-personal Information is collected in order to:
           Use it for statistical and research purposes and for customization and improvement of our Site's
            interface.
    Personal Information is collected in order to:
           Be able to reply to the User's questions and concerns which were sent by the Users to
            ironSource's service center.
           Be able to contact Users for the purpose of providing them with technical assistance and
            support.
           sign you up for the Service
           provide the Site
           Determine general geolocation information (i.e., country) from which the User's computer is
            connected to the Internet in order for us to know the general location of our Site's Users as well
            as in order to safeguard our Site.
5.      Sharing Information with Third Parties
    ironSource will not share any Personal Information it collects with any third party. Notwithstanding,
    ironSource may disclose Personal Information in the following cases: (a) to satisfy any applicable law,
    regulation, legal process, subpoena or governmental request; (b) to enforce this Privacy Policy,
    including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address
    fraud, security or technical issues; (d) to respond to User's support requests; (e) respond to claims that
    any content available on the Site violates the rights of third-parties; (f) to respond to claims that contact
    information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without
    their consent or as a form of harassment; (g) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of
    ironSource, its Users, or the general public; (h) when ironSource is undergoing any change in control,
    including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets; or (i) to
    collect, hold and/or manage your Personal Information through ironSource’s authorized third party
    service providers (for example, Amazon cloud services), as reasonable for business purposes, which
    may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction; (j)
    pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure; or (k) cooperate with third parties for the
    purpose of enhancing the User's experience.
    For avoidance of doubt, ironSource may transfer and disclose Non-personal Information to third
    parties at its own discretion.
6.      Deletion or deletion of Personal Information
   If for any reason you wish to modify or delete your Personal Information please send us an email to:
   legal@ironsrc.com and we will make reasonable efforts to modify or delete any such Personal
   Information pursuant to any applicable privacy laws.
7.      Minors
   To use of Site, you must be over the age of thirteen (13). Therefore, ironSource does not knowingly
   collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and does not wish to do so.
   We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age
   of thirteen (13) are not using the Site.
8.      Security

    We take a great care in implementing and maintaining the security of ironSource's Site and its User's
    Personal Information. The Personal Information is hosted on the Amazon Cloud which provides
    advanced security features. ironSource employs industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the
    safety of its Users’ Personal Information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information.
    However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized access will never occur.
9.       Third Party Software/Service
    While using the Site we may be using third party software and/or service, in order to collect and/or
    process the information detailed herein. Such software includes without limitation, Google Analytics,
    which privacy policy is available at http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html
    and Amazon cloud services which privacy policy can be found at: http://aws.amazon.com/privacy/.
10. Third Party Sites
    While using the Site you may encounter links to third party websites. Please be advised that such third
    party websites are independent sites, and we assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever with
    regard to privacy matters or any other legal matter with respect to such sites. We encourage you to
    carefully read the privacy policies and the terms of use or service of such websites.
11. International Data Transfer
    We may transfer information collected about you, including Personal Information, to affiliated entities,
    or to other third party service providers (as provided herein) across borders and from your
    country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Please note that we
    may transfer such information to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data
    protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to such transfer of information.
12. Cookies
    When you access or use the Site, we may use industry-wide technologies such as "cookies" and local
    storage, such as Flash (or similar technologies), which stores certain local information on your device
    ("Local Storage") and which may enable, inter alia, automatic activation of certain features, and make
    your experience much more relevant, convenient and effortless. Such information is locally stored in
    your device. The Company may access such information. The Company may use both session cookies
    (which expire once you close the Hosting Application) and persistent cookies (which stay on the User’s
    device until he/she deletes them). Such Local Storage used by the Service may store non-personal
    information (such as the different pages viewed by a User within the Hosting Application) as well as
    User persistent identifier and geo-location data, which will be collected in accordance with the terms
    specified herein. It is easy to prohibit and/or delete the Local Storage, inter alia, via uninstalling the
    Hosting Application from your mobile device and/or through the settings options of your device. Most
    platforms will allow you to erase cookies from a device, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a
    warning before a cookie is stored. In order to erase or disable the Local Storage option you may use the
    settings option of your device or according to the specific instructions provided by the third party
    service provider's privacy policy and terms of use. However, if you block or erase cookies, or change
    the settings of your device, your experience may be affected and may be limited.
13.      Changes to the Privacy Policy
    The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Site and any information collected therein.
    ironSource reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently.
    We will provide notice of substantial changes of this policy on the homepage of the Site and/or we will
    send you an e-mail regarding such changes to the e-mail address that you may have provided us with.
    Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on our Site or
    sent by email. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last

    Revised” date and your continued use of the Site after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance
    of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.
14.      Have any Questions?
    If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to send us
    an email at: legal@ironsrc.com and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe:
